Madhavi Dnyandeo Jejurkar (1) Featured



Software Developer seeking roles in Software Engineering, Software Development, Full Stack Development, Project Management, Change Management, Defect Management, Quality Management, Requirement Gathering, Application Support, JavaScript, Bootstrap, ¡Query, HTML



Current Designation: Software Developer Total Experience: 0 Year(s) 9 Month(s)

Current Company: Capgemini Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: PG Diploma [Computers]

Pref. Location: Pune, Mumbai Suburbs, Navi Mumbai Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Engineering, Software Development, Full Stack Development, Project Management, Change Management, Defect Management, Quality Management, Requirement Gathering, Application

Support, JavaScript, Bootstrap, ¡Query, Eclipse, MySQL, HTML, CSS

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Software Engineer with 1 years of experience in Software Development.

department in analysis, design and development in .Net framework.

Experience in developing UI pages using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.

Experience in API testing using postman and SoapUI.

Proficient to work with positive attitude and perform under demanding conditions and meeting tight

deadlines while working in diverse environments.

Vibrant team player with belief in taking positive approach towards issue resolution.

Have sound knowledge on Unit testing/SIT and creation of Unit test case documents

Looking for a challenging career in a premier and fast-growing organization where I can gain new knowledge and sharpen my skills and put my best efforts to hold a position of responsibilities and workout something better for achieving organizational and individual goal.

Work Experience

Capgemini as Software Developer

Oct 2019 to Till Date

Capgemini Technologies Service Ltd as Software Developer

Oct 2019 to Jul 2020

3M-Lumos Health Project

In this project data related to cleanliness in area was maintained using a device called Luminometer and the reading captured by the luminometer were populated on the UI pages and record was maintained in Database.

Project Details

Duration: 18 Oct 2019 - 23 July 2020 Project: 3M-Lumos Health Project Role: Front End Developer Project Scope & Responsibilities

Creation of UI Web Pages using JavaScript, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS technologies

Creation of Rest API using .Net Technology.

Testing of Rest API using Postman and UI pages using JMeter.

Responsible for development and testing the interfaces.

Onshore/offshore coordination.

Involved in the Code Review process and creation of TDD, UT documents.

CDAC Project- Local Fish Basket

In coastal area fisher men and women have to go to every place to sell fishes. Customers do not get fishes on time because of the huge demand and the women who sale fishes cannot reach in all the places. To reduce the efforts of those fish sellers, we created website so that customers can buy fish according to their choice.

Project Details Duration: 1 Month Project: Local Fish Basket Role: Software Developer

Responsible for development and testing the interfaces. Creation of class diagram, ER diagram using Star UML. Creation of Web Pages using HTML, CSS, bootstrap. Responsible for resolving defects at the time of Unit Testing.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Pravara Rural College of Engineering, Pune University in 2018

PG: PG Diploma (Computers) from Centre for Development of Advanced Computing (CDAC) in 2019

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Advance computing certificate -CDAC

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Windows 7, Windows 10, CSS.	
Core Java, .Net, Eclipse, Visual Studio	
JavaScript, PHP, Bootstrap, HTML	
SVN Repository, GIT, MySQL, SQL.	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent / Temporary

Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time